srx.com.sg 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy - Singapore Real Estate Exchange (SRX)

* **Who We Are:**

StreetSine Technology Group Pte. Ltd. is an indirect subsidiary of Singapore Press Holdings Ltd (SPH). Through StreetSine Singapore Pte. Ltd. or our other subsidiaries or affiliates from time-to-time ("we" or "us" or "our") offer products on or in connection with our:

  * websites including [www.srx.com.sg](https://www.srx.com.sg/), [www stproperty.sg](https://www.stproperty.sg/) [www.streetsine.com](http://www.streetsine.com/) (collectively the "Websites"), and
  * Applications, including SRX Property, mySG Home, Agent Connect, SRX Analyzer and Mortgage Connect (collectively, the "Apps").

* **Our Commitment to Privacy**

We are committed to safeguarding your personal data across all our Websites and Applications. Our Privacy Policy (read together with our Terms of Service) sets out how personal data provided by you, or we may collect from you, may be used, processed or disclosed by us, including how certain information may be used to personalise advertising to best reflect your interests. 

Our Privacy Policy explains not only the types of personal data we collect, but how we secure your data, and how you can access and update data secured with us. This Policy regulates the use of our Websites, Apps, and any other means by which you may need to connect or interact with us, to make use of our products and services (collectively, "Services").

You agree that personal data relating to you which is collected by us, or provided by you, may from time to time be used, processed, and disclosed for such purposes and to such persons as set out in this Privacy Policy. Nothing in this Policy negates your statutory legal protections. 

We may amend our Privacy Policy at any time by posting a revised version on our Website. You will be deemed to have knowledge of and agreed to the amended Privacy Policy if, after revision, you continue to use the Website, the Apps or our Services. 

We advise that you may wish to regularly review our Privacy Policy to keep up to date with any revisions that may from time to time take place. We may revise our Policy for reasons such as keeping pace with regulatory changes or improving the services we provide to our customers.

* **What Information We Collect**

When you use our Services, we may collect a variety of information from you. That information may be about you, your devices or your interaction with our Services. Some of this information may identify you directly or could be used to potentially identify you in combination with other data.

* **When You Choose to Share**

When you use our Services, you may be asked to provide personal information. This might be your name or contact information, information for applications for products and/or services, to facilitate payment, or details about your own home or other properties that you own, rent or may be interested in. Sometimes you may be asked to supply financial information. 

Some examples might be if:

  1. you decide to register with us, or subscribe to our Services, or request email notifications or newsletters via our Websites or Apps; or
  2. you choose to carry out transactions with us on or in relation to our Websites or Apps; or
  3. you complete other forms or transactions, such as calculators, or applications for products or services; or
  4. you correspond with a real estate professional (such as a real estate agent or broker, mortgage lender or loan officer, property manager, investor, homebuilder, or others) via the Services; or
  5. you request assistance from our customer services or sales teams, whether that be by email, telephone or face to face; or
  6. you have asked a third party to contact us and share information on your behalf; or
  7. you choose to submit personal data to us for any other reason.

You may also provide information about a third party through the Services, for example, if you choose to share a real estate listing with a friend or family member via SMS or email.

* **Use of Cookies or TMs**

When you access or use our Websites or Apps, cookies or other automatic tracking mechanisms ("TMs") may collect or analyse anonymised information. This information may record the number of users or their frequency of use, the number of times a page has been viewed, often referred to as "impressions", as well as automatically logging analysis, calculations, or points of access or departure. 

Using cookies helps us improve the quality of Service you receive. It helps us by better identifying what information you're most interested in, by tracking trends and measuring advertising effectiveness, or by storing information you may wish to retrieve on a regular basis, such as shortlisted properties or preferred searches.

Our use of cookies involves a small data file being sent to your browser to store and track aggregated information about you when you enter our Websites or Apps. As indicated cookies may track the number of users or their frequency of use, their profiles or preferred sites. 

We may use a third party to measure and analyse usage across our Websites or Apps. They will collate aggregated information such as the number of impressions and unique visitors, their average collective time spent on a Websites or Apps or common access and departure points. Our websites may be coded with software that facilitates a third party in tracking and collating information. 

Aggregated information from any third party is provided to us as a tool to assist in analysing usage of our Websites, Apps and Services. Such anonymised aggregated data may also be available to media organisations or research companies for the purposes of conducting industry comparisons with other service providers. 

Should you wish to disable these cookies, you may do so by changing the setting on your browser. This may impact of your ability to take full advantage of our free services. 

* **Using Your Mobile**

Remember you are also able to disable cookies on your mobile phone and revise your privacy settings to not permit any site you visit to log information such as your location via your mobile phone. 

* **Why we Collect Information**

No-one is required to provide personal data as a condition of using our Websites or Apps, except as may be necessary for us to be able to provide services or products which you purchase or access through the same, or respond to your requests, or where you contact us directly. If you wish, you may choose to browse the Websites or Apps without making disclosures. 

When you provide us with data it may be used in an aggregated form or individually or made be combined with other information to help us optimise the management and operation of our Websites, Apps and services. In turn that helps us enhance your browsing experience. 

Some of the reasons we might use information you've provided us might be; to respond to a query you've made, verify your identity, prevent crime, review or analyse our processes, or meet or comply with our legal obligations. We may also need to use information you've provided for other reasons, for example; to process applications for subscriptions or other services, maintain accounts with us, to enable us to provide you with services, to communicate with you about those products and services or undertake statistical analysis and market research.

It may also be necessary to disclose personal data you've shared to professional advisors, or service providers to comply with legal requirements, or comply with our Terms of Use, or to protect the rights of others, whether they be other users or those of our affiliates or subsidiaries, or in connection with a business asset transaction. 

* **Third Party Websites**

Our Websites may contain links to websites operated by a third party. As we are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party, we advise that you take the time to familiarise yourself with their Privacy Policy and their Terms of Use, to better understand how they may collect or secure your personal data. 

It's worth remembering that a third party website may be co-branded with our logo or trademark even if they are not operated or maintained by us. 

* **Keeping Information Safe**

Any information we receive is secured in hosted databases. We will always take reasonable steps to protect the information you share with us, including, but not limited to, setup of processes, equipment and software to avoid unauthorised access or disclosure of this information. 

Do not share any passwords you may use to access any of our accounts or services and do consider changing your passwords at regular intervals. 

Personal Information will only be made available to our employees when reasonably required to assist you in accessing or using our services or products. 

* **Withdrawing Consent or Making Corrections**

If you wish to withdraw your consent at any time in respect of the collection, use or disclosure by us of personal data, you may contact our designated Data Protection officer.

Similarly, if you wish to make correct an error or omission in any personal data secured by us, in our possession or under our control, you too may contact the same designated Data Protection Officer. 

Requests should be made by email to [DataProtectionOfficer@srx.com.sg](mailto:DataProtectionOfficer@srx.com.sg)

StreetSine Pte Ltd

1008 Toa Payoh North

#05-17/18

Singapore 318996

* **Compliance**

Our Privacy Policy complies with the Laws of Singapore and is Protection of Personal Data Act 2012 compliant.

* **Disclaimer**

We shall not be liable for any voluntary disclosure or personal data made by you to other users in connection with the use of our Websites or Apps.
